Arafat Mia

Address: Mohammadpur, Dhaka Bangladesh.

Phone: +8801318452438

Mail: arafatsorkar12345@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/arafatsorkar

GitHub: https://github.com/Arafatsorkar1

GitHub: https://github.com/Arafatsorkar12



Carrier Objective:

I enjoy web development, and I have 2 years+ of experience in developing web applications, and expertise of HTML, CSS, bootstrap, Php, MySql, PostgreSQL, Ajax and most popular JS & Laravel PHP framework as like Front-end & Back-end. You can have a look at my work experience related to these languages from the following details.

Technical Skills:

HTML & CSS3 **MySQL**

Bootstrap5 Framework PostGreSQL

PHP (OOP) Rest API

Laravel Framework Ajax

Java-Script React is

Competitive Programming

Professional Experience:

Junior Laravel Developer

Smart Software Ltd.

05/2023 - Present Dhaka, Bangladesh

Error correction is the most popular and demanding job. Which is my main responsibility. I work on Govt projects. I work on the Payment System and Account Module.

Software Engineering Intern

Bangla Soft

There Have Web Based Software. i Developed web-based software.

Software Developer (Part-Time)

Soft Park IT

09/2022 - 03/2023 Dhaka, Bangladesh

I worked on e-commerce management systems

02/2023 - 05/2023 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Hospital management System

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascriptc, React, MySQL, bootstrap

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Emergency, Indoor, Out Door, Prescription, Pharmacy, Accounts, Nurse Station, Payment

Section, O.T section, Clearance Section.

Ecommerce web

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: single vendor web, Here is a beautiful home page for displaying products with different pages depending on the product, and online payment gateway. The delivery system is on. Products can be

controlled from order receipt to delivery

Service and shop web

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Using PHP Laravel, HTML, CSS, JS, SQL, and bootstrap, This is a service side, here the admin will publish his service and the user will answer some of their questions, depending on the answer the user will be made the service head.

POS

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, PostGreSQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement : selling cart system, payment system, and product return system, which I did with design, and also solved some account problems and code bugs It has a sales system, and a product return system, all of which I have not done. I worked on bar code

Inventory Management System

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Bug Fixing Almost All Module, Stock Manage, Report Manage, Sale, Return,

Package Product, Serial Product Purchase, etch

ERP

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Product Create, Stock Manage, Sale Chalan, gate Pass, Invoice Section, Error

Fixing

CRM

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Mail section, Relation Invoice Section

Job Portal

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, bootstrap, SQL

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement : office Project. Here there is the company profile, there is the employee profile, and the job circular will be given by the. company and it will be notified to the employee in between the

notification. Imply has a CV-keeping system, everything is accounted

Usd-invest Trading Web Application:

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL, Apache2

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Create new users and they deposit their account and then they can trade here for

profit. from the admin panel, an admin can monitor all trading.

Nagarikseba Web Application:

Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL, Apache2

Framework: Laravel

Key Achievement: Create a user using sms to verify, Apply for a trade license, holding license, and give

users the approval and certificate of the license. Nagad Payment and Accounts Manage. Nagad

And Bkash Getaway

Academic Qualification:

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and Engineering

2023

State University of Bangladesh, Dhaka Bangladesh

Certificates:

1. Certification: PHP with Laravel

Institute: Bangladesh Association of Software & Information Services (BASIS)

Location: BDBL Bhaban (4th Floor), 12 Kawran Bazar, Dhaka

2. Certification: Skill Development For Mobile Game & Application

Institute: ICT Division.

Description: Participation for attending a two hundred hours of training for mobile application

development

SUB Code-Byte programming contest V1.0

Description: Inter university contest 4. SUB Computing club 1/22 – 12/22

Language Proficiency:

Bengali (Reading: High, writing: High, Speaking: High)
English (Reading: High, writing: High, Speaking: Medium)